<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: VC2 | Dale Race - Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://racedale.github.io/blog/categories/vc2/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://racedale.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-26T12:19:38-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://racedale.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Dale Race]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAE Banner]]></title>
    <link href="http://racedale.github.io/blog/2014/01/29/mae-banner/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-29T12:06:14-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://racedale.github.io/blog/2014/01/29/mae-banner</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is the banner for mae.truman.edu to accompany the MAE Poster.</p>

<p><img src="/images/posts/mae_banner.png" title="MAE Banner" alt="MAE Banner" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAE Poster]]></title>
    <link href="http://racedale.github.io/blog/2014/01/28/mae-poster/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-28T19:14:47-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://racedale.github.io/blog/2014/01/28/mae-poster</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We had to redesign the horrible advertisement for the Truman MAE program.  I went with a photographic approach and put an apple on some books and took pics of it at the library in front of a chalkboard.  I played around with the idea of writing the advertisement on the chalkboard but if I did that it would be harder to remove if I did it wrong than to just put white text on a clean chalkboard. After this we learned how to do the spot color channels in photoshop which more or less just makes me want to not use photos for 2 color projects.<br/>
<img src="/images/posts/mae_poster.jpg" title="MAE Poster" alt="MAE Poster" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[APO Service Ad]]></title>
    <link href="http://racedale.github.io/blog/2014/01/20/apo-service-ad/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-20T19:47:59-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://racedale.github.io/blog/2014/01/20/apo-service-ad</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The assignment was to redesign a poster we found on campus.  The one I did was an advertisement for APO volunteering to help other organizations.  I kept the same idea of having the logo in the middle, which apparently is good for making it easier to remember who the poster is for.  With the old one the hierarchy didn&rsquo;t go along with the message so I made mine so that first you read &lsquo;let&rsquo;s team up&rsquo; then the apo logo, then you go down to the block of information.  Having it tilted by 20 degrees makes it a little more interesting to look at and eye catching, without affecting the readability like 45 degrees would to make your head tilt.<br/>
<img src="/images/posts/apo_service_ad.jpg" title="APO Service Ad" alt="APO Service AD" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
