<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: VC3 | Dale Race - Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://racedale.github.io/blog/categories/vc3/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://racedale.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-06T21:19:16-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://racedale.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Dale Race]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solar Website]]></title>
    <link href="http://racedale.github.io/blog/2014/02/10/solar-website/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-10T15:32:05-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://racedale.github.io/blog/2014/02/10/solar-website</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I spent a lot of time over the past week researching web design and working on our first real project in VisComm 3.  I choose to take a 960.gs approach because after doing some research it became apparent that it was previously a popular way to do web design prior to the responsive web design stuff.  It is a psd file that has columns set up already, you design the website in photoshop, and then use css to layout your site according to how you did it in photoshop.  I figured that since we are all about using grids for print design, it makes sense to use them for web layout as well.  I went with a 12 column grid.</p>

<p>The hardest trouble I had was with javascript.  I&rsquo;m not familiar with it.  I want to have some practical javascript not just some simple little button.  I went about trying to implement Fancybox into the website and spent many hours trying to get it to work.  Eventually I figured it out, the code I used had an extra javascript(); once I took that out it started working.  I went on to use Fancybox for the images and to open and iFrame to load a youtube video.</p>

<p>I really liked the approach of trying to design a website the way a real web designer would have, the tutorials I watched were incredibly valuable.  I had more fun watching the tutorials and learning the pracices than I did actually doing my own work.  For the next project I want to take the same approach, but learn responsive design.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
